https://allmanbrothersband.com/terms-of-service/

Who we are
Hittin’ The Web Group, LLC (“Hittin’ The Web Group“) (“us,” “our,” “we”) operates AllmanBrothersBand.com (“site,” “website”) on behalf of The ABB Merchandising Co., Inc.  Hittin’ The Web Group, LLC may be reached via the Contact form on this website or by mail at 11485 S NC Highway 119, Burlington, NC 27217.
Non-Personally-Identifying Information
Like most website operators, we collect non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request.  Our purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how website visitors use this website. From time to time, we may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of this website.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
If you register to create an account on our site, contact us via the contact form, sign up for our newsletter, or leave comments or upload images or files to this site, we collect some or all of the following personal information:
Username – used to login to our site to use certain features such as leaving comments or uploading picturesEmail Address – used to contact you to complete your registration or to recover your password.  We may also email you to tell you about website updates, such as to our terms of service or this Privacy Policy.Statement of why you’d like to join — used to detect spammers
Optionally, if you register to create an account on this site you may provide:Mobile phone number – as a way to contact you for the same reasons we use email, as outlined in this policyLocation – to determine if website or marketing information such as concert dates or merchandise availability is relevant to youZip or Postal Code – for the same reasons we use Country as described aboveSignature – free-form text to appear under your posts
Optionally, if you use the site’s Private Message system to send private messages to other site users, we store your message in our database along with the username of the recipient.
If you sign up to receive the Allman Brothers Band Fan Newsletter (“the Peach-O-Gram”), we collect:
Email address – to send you the newsletter and to identify your record if you decide to unsubscribeEmail opens, clicks or opt-ins – to help decide whether the information we send in our newsletter is interesting or relevant to you
We also collect:
IP Address – to detect or prevent spam
Passwords
If you register an account with us, you must provide a password that you will use to login to your account on our website.  Please use a unique password and do not use a password that you use with any other website, system or service.   By providing us with a password, you confirm that we cannot be held liable for any damages caused by use of that password anywhere else.
Comments
Throughout this document, we use the term “comment” and “comments” to refer to any information that a logged-in site visitor uploads to the site, including but not limited to comments on news stories, blog posts, pictures, discography items, forum posts, and guest book posts. When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
If you contact us via our website’s Contact form, we collect your name, email address and any other information you enter into that form.  We use this information to respond to your inquiry and we may store that information until you ask us to delete it.  We do not use information supplied on the contact form for marketing purposes.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. We use cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their usage of this website, and their website access preferences. Visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using our websites, with the drawback that certain features of our websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year. If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser. When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website. These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Our Apache web server keeps log files that track the requests your browser makes for pages, images and other website assets.  It stores the IP address from which each request was made. We use website analytics software packages to analyze these log files to understand how this site is being accessed and to help us improve it.  At various times we have used, and may in the future use, Google Analytics, Webalizer, AWStats, and Analog to analyze these log files.  The statistics provided by these analytics packages are aggregated and to the extent that they do not contain personally-identifiable information, may be shared with others to understand website traffic.
Who we share your data with
We disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of our employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf or to provide services available at Hittin’ The Web Group’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Hittin’ The Web Group’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Hittin’ The Web Group will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Hittin’ The Web Group discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Hittin’ The Web Group believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Hittin’ The Web Group, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Hittin’ The Web Group website and have supplied your email address, Hittin’ The Web Group may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Hittin’ The Web Group and our products.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. We may use this to recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.   For users that register on our website or subscribe to our newsletter, we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information. This information is stored indefinitely unless you ask us to delete it.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes. You may request deletion, rectification, or access to your data, by emailing privacy@hittintheweb.com specifying any action you wish us to take, or by using the Personal Data Management page at https://allmanbrothersband.com/blog/pdm/
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service. We store your data on our web server at LiquidWeb’s data center in Lansing, MI, USA.  We send backups of our web server, including your data, to Microsoft’s OneDrive cloud data storage service.   These backups are stored on a rotating basis and not retained longer than 30 days.  If you request a change or deletion of your data, your data in our backups will be updated or deleted within 30 days. LiquidWeb’s Privacy Policy is available on their website, and their Data Protection Agreement is available request from us.  Microsoft’s Privacy Policy is available on their website, and their Online Service Terms, also available on their website, details their data protection policy.
Your contact information
If you have questions about privacy-specific concerns, you may reach us via our Contact form or by emailing info@hittintheweb.com.
Additional information
What data breach procedures we have in place
If we determine that a data breach has taken place, we will advise you via email and let you know what personal data may have been compromised and what steps we are taking to remedy the breach and prevent further occurrences.
Business Transfers
If Hittin’ The Web Group, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Hittin’ The Web Group goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Hittin’ The Web Group may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.
Ads
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Hittin’ The Web Group and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, we may change our Privacy Policy from time to time, and in our sole discretion. We encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to our Privacy Policy. If you have a AllmanBrothersBand.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Version: 1.1 – Updated for GDPR ComplianceDate: May 24, 2018
ALLMAN BROTHERS BAND name, ALLMAN BROTHERS name, likenesses, logos, mushroom design and peach truck are all registered trademarks of ABB MERCHANDISING CO., INC. whose rights are specifically reserved. Any artwork, visual, or audio representations used on this web site CONTAINING ANY REGISTERED TRADEMARKS are under license from ABB MERCHANDISING CO., INC. A REVOCABLE, GRATIS LICENSE IS GRANTED TO ALL REGISTERED PEACH CORP MEMBERS FOR THE DOWNLOADING OF ONE COPY FOR PERSONAL USE ONLY. ANY DISTRIBUTION OR REPRODUCTION OF THE TRADEMARKS CONTAINED HEREIN ARE PROHIBITED AND ARE SPECIFICALLY RESERVED BY ABB MERCHANDISING CO.,INC.
Privacy Policy
Terms of Service
Report Infringement
Contact Us
site by Hittin’ The Web Group, LLC with www.experiencewasabi3d.com
Facebook
Twitter
Youtube
Instagram
